You talked about how you don't want Israel, you're saying re-Israel, that October the 7th happened, you're placing that in historical context, I understand that.
Please don't say that again, we don't have time for it. You've made that point five times already.
I don't know what you have time for. Let me explain my opinion.
For the love of God, let me finish a sentence, man. Maybe you're not used to women talking, I don't know.
But I'd like to finish a sentence, sir. Anyway, so...
No, you are misleading the public now by explaining this thing that you just said.
I'm not even going to bother trying to answer. If you don't think Israel's reaction is acceptable, what would have been an acceptable reaction to you?
You've got 10 seconds left.
To end occupation and allow peace to prevail for both people.
That's their reaction. Brilliant. Yeah. Sorry to have been a woman speaking to you, but there you are. Dr. Mustafa Bogati.
You know, I find this interview to have been quite impressive.
Because this woman, Julia Hartley, whatever, was able to just demonstrate incredible versatility in it.
She managed in one interview to simultaneously be a twat, a sod, a wanker, a minge, a tosser, full-fledged nutter.
Crikey! Chaz! Julia, Chaz!
You're top of the pops!
She's actually the personification of absolute white woman bullshit.
Trying to pull feminism out of her neck while absolutely not giving a goddamn about all of the women in Palestine.
Look at that face.
Mm, mm, mm.
You're top of the pops!
...